Guide to the Robert K. Merton Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Reference and Research, 1933-2002
  - Series V: Reference and Research, 1933-2002
    - Index Cards
      - Priorities--General (Box 384)
      - Concept of Genius in Science (Box 384)
      - Multiple Discoveries by Same Scientists (Box 384)
      - Notes--Mostly Used in Introduction on the History of Systematics in Social Theory (Box 384)
      - Puritanism and Science (Box 384)
      - Seventeenth Century Odds and Ends (Box 384)
      - Age Stratification in Science (Box 384)
      - Multiples, Anticipations in Social Science (Box 385)
      - Quotations and Literary References (Box 385)
      - Culture Diffusion (Box 385)
      - Luck, Fortune and Chance (Box 385)
      - Banalization (Box 385)
      - Thumbnail Biographies (Box 385)
      - History of Social Theory (Box 385)
      - Functions: History of Theory (Box 385)
      - Marx, Karl (Box 385)
      - Approaches to History of Theory (Box 385)
      - Theorizing as Decisional Behavior (Box 385)
      - Theory and Hypothesis (Box 385)
      - Method (Box 385)
      - Simple Idea, Major Theory (Empty) (Box 385)
      - The Interview (Box 385)
      - Nineteenth Century Polls and Surveys (Box 385)
      - Observation (Box 385)
      - Non-Contemporaneity of Contemporaneous (Box 385)
      - Concepts and Conceptual Schemes (Box 385)
      - Models (Box 385)
      - Theory: Types and Criteria (Box 385)
      - Emulation in Science (Box 385)
      - Tools: Impact on Science (Box 385)
      - Deviant Case Analysis (Box 385)
      - Levels Analysis (Box 385)
      - Logical Fallacies in Sociology (Box 385)
      - Indices, Signs (Box 385)
      - State of System (Box 385)
      - Empirical Generalizations (Box 385)
      - Qualitative Analysis (Box 385)
      - Confirmation: Proof (Box 385)
      - Predictions (Box 385)
      - Case Study- Life History (Box 385)
      - Codification and Derivation (Box 385)
      - Convergence in Theory (Box 385)
      - Follow-Up: Taking Concepts Seriously (Box 385)
      - Explanation, Cause (Box 385)
      - Measurement (Box 385)
      - Typology (Box 385)
      - Psycho-Social Approach to Economic Theory (Empty) (Box 385)
      - Angell Restudy (Box 385)
      - Ritualism-Retreatism Responses (Box 385)
      - Puritanism: Components and Types (Empty) (Box 386)
      - Problematics (Box 386)
      - Problem-Finding in Sociology (Box 386)
      - Problem-Analysis (Box 386)
      - Problem: Ingredients (Box 386)
      - Social Contexts of Sociological Problems (Box 386)
      - Problem: Rationale (Box 386)
      - Specialization in Sociology: Problems (Box 386)
      - Problem: Contradictory Findings (Empty) (Box 386)
      - Intra-Disciplinary Influences on Problem-Finding (Empty) (Box 386)
      - Stages of Sociology and Problems (Empty) (Box 386)
      - Social Contexts of Sociological Problems (Box 386)
      - Plausibility-Truth Relations (Box 386)
      - Theories of the Middle Range (Box 386)
      - Role-Sequence (Box 386)
      - Elegiac vs. Interchangeable Theories (Empty) (Box 386)
      - Social Climates (Empty) (Box 386)
      - Insider-Outsider (Box 386)
      - Concept of Problem (Box 386)
      - Applied Social Research: Types (Box 386)
      - Pure and Applied Research (Box 386)
      - Expert in Bureaucracy (Box 386)
      - Climate of Opinion in Science (Empty) (Box 386)
      - Foci of Research (Box 386)
      - Forecasts and Predictions (Box 386)
      - Origination of Applied Research (Box 386)
      - Specialization in Science (Box 386)
      - Research and Decision Making (Box 386)
      - Risk Taking in Decision and Research (Box 386)
      - Time and Research (Empty) (Box 386)
      - Fiduciary Role of Expert (Box 386)
      - Government Sponsored Research (Box 386)
      - Applied Research-Specific Cases (Box 386)
      - Anti-Intellectualism (Box 386)
      - Technology, Worker and Engineer (Box 386)
      - Ideology
        - General (Box 386)
        - Concept of (Box 386)
        - History of (Box 386)
        - Examples (Box 386)
        - Functions of (Box 386)
        - As Corrosive (Box 386)
      - Propaganda (Box 386)
      - Social Structure and Anomie
        - 1--Concept of Anomie (Box 386)
        - 2--Measures of Anomie (Box 386)
        - 3--Alternatives to Anomic Response (Box 386)
        - 4--Success Emphasis (Box 386)
        - 5--Aspirations (Box 386)
        - 6--Responses to Anomie (Box 386)
        - 7--Innovation (Box 386)
        - 8--Ritualism (Box 386)
        - 9--Retreatism (Box 386)
        - 10--Ressentiment (Box 386)
        - 11--Rebellion (Box 386)
        - Over-Conformity (Box 386)
        - Debunking and Distrust (Box 386)
        - Nonconformity (Box 386)
        - Power (Box 386)
        - Social Stratification (Box 387)
        - Social Mobility (Box 387)
        - Class Structure (Box 387)
        - Social Adaptation (Box 387)
        - Symbolism (Box 387)
        - Psycho-Analysis (Box 387)
        - Alienation (Box 387)
        - Identification (Box 387)
        - Conflict (Box 387)
        - Frustration (Box 387)
        - Humor (Box 387)
        - Emotion, Sociology of (Box 387)
        - Jealousy (Box 387)
        - Definitions and Theories (Box 387)
        - Anxiety, Fear, Anger and Stress (Box 387)
        - Money (Box 387)
        - Leisure and "Busyness" (Box 387)
        - Phatic Communion (Box 387)
        - Pluralistic Ignorance (Empty) (Box 387)
        - Unscheduled Events
          - General (Box 387)
          - Disasters (Empty) (Box 387)
      - Housing Study--Patterns of Social Life: Explorations in the Sociology of Housing
        - Sociology of Space (Box 387)
        - Research Program on Social Life in Housing Developments (Box 387)
        - Chapter I: Moving In
          - 1. New Tenant in the New Community (Box 387)
          - 2. Social Status of Public Housing: Opinions Without Fact (Box 387)
          - 3. Figment of a 'Typical' Housing Development (Empty) (Box 387)
        - Chapter II: Diversities in Public Housing: Craftown
          - 1. Social Atmosphere of a Workers Community (Box 387)
          - 2. Pioneers and Latecomers: Contrasts in Motivation (Box 387)
          - 3. Challenge of a Worker's Community (Box 387)
          - 3. Occupational Worlds of Hilltown Negroes and Whites (Box 387)
          - 4. Social Contexts of Orientations Toward Hilltown (Box 387)
          - 5. First Orientations of Negroes and Whites (Empty)
            - a. Expectations of Relations Between the Races (Empty) (Box 387)
            - b. Expectations of Permanence or Transiency (Box 387)
          - 6. First Social Contacts Between the Races (Empty) (Box 387)
          - 7. Early Foci of Attention Among Residents (Empty) (Box 387)
          - 8. Early Evaluations of the Community by Residents (Box 387)
        - Chapter III: Diversities in Public Housing: Hilltown
          - 1. Social Atmosphere of a Biracial Community (Box 387)
          - 2. Double Meaning of Housing for Negroes (Box 387)
        - Chapter IV: The Networks of Interpersonal Relations
          - 1. Neighbors and Friends (Box 387)
          - 2. Spatial Patterns of Personal Relations (Box 387)
          - 3. Social Status and Personal Relations (Box 387)
          - 4. Group Differences, Spatial Adjacency and Personal Relations (Box 387)
          - 5. Striking Roots in the Community: Personal Relations and Tenant Morale (Empty) (Box 387)
        - Chapter V: Dynamics of Race Relations in Hilltown
          - 1. Previous Contacts Between the Races (Box 387)
          - 2.Race Relations: Expectations vs. Actuality (Box 387)
          - 3. Reciprocal Images of the Races (Box 387)
          - 4. Types of Interracial Adjustment (Box 387)
          - 5. Signs of Change (Box 387)
          - 6. Conditions of Change in Race Relations (Box 387)
          - 7. Social Psychology of Racial "Invasion" (Box 387)
        - Chapter VI: Grassroots Politics: Civic Action and Apathy
          - 1. Mass Apathy in Politics (Box 387)
          - 2. Political Atmospheres: Craftown and Hilltown (Box 387)
          - 3. Roots of Political and Civic Interest (Box 387)
          - 4. Anatomy of Political Action (Box 387)
          - 5. Political Conflict: Corollary of Political Concern (Box 387)
          - 6. Parochialism or Integration with Environing Community (Box 387)
          - 7. Transfer of Local Political Interest to Larger Political Scene (Box 387)
          - 8. Politics as a Social Catalyst (Box 387)
          - 9. Civic Apathy and Civic Concern: A Summary (Empty) (Box 387)
        - Chapter VII: Patterns of Popular Participation
          - 1. Emerging Patterns of Community Participation (Box 387)
          - 2. Degrees of Participation (Empty) (Box 387)
          - 3. Intensity of Participation (Box 387)
          - 4. Social Participation: New Experience or an Old Habit? (Box 387)
          - 5. Organized Group Life and Personal Ties (Box 387)
          - 6. Social Participation: New Role for Working Class Women (Box 387)
          - 7. Caste and Class in Social Participation (Empty)
            - a. The Negro's Role in Hilltown (Empty) (Box 387)
            - b. White-Collar Participant in Worker's Community of Craftown (Box 387)
          - 8. Professional Leadership: Group Worker in Hilltown (Box 387)
          - 9. Structure of Local Leadership (Box 387)
          - 10. Role of the Community Center (Box 387)
        - Chapter VIII: Social Value of Privacy (Box 388)
          - 1. Privacy: Past and Present (Box 388)
          - 2. Meanings of Privacy (Box 388)
          - 3. Privacy of Anonymity (Box 388)
          - 4. Privacy of Social Distance (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 5. Seasonal Variations in Privacy (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 6. Privacy and Family Life (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 7. Privacy and Architectural Design (Box 388)
        - Chapter IX: Role of Management
          - 1. Housing Management: Servant or Master? (Box 388)
          - 2. Social Psychology of Graded Rent (Box 388)
          - 3. Management and the Social Psychology of Tenant Maintenance (Box 388)
          - 4. Regulations: Regimentation or Freedom? (Box 388)
          - 5. Social Factors in Tenant Appraisal of Management (Box 388)
          - 6. Tenant Contact with Management Staff
            - a. Functions of Social Contact (Box 388)
        - Chapter X: Environment of Opinion: Public Images of Public Housing
          - 1. Prevailing Images of Public Housing
            - a. Class Composition (Box 388)
            - b. Race Composition (Box 388)
            - c. Government as Landlord (Box 388)
            - d. Economic Goals of Residents (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 2. Exposure of Residents to Climate of Opinion (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 3. Climate of Opinion and Tenant Morale (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 4. Opinion Environments: Primary and Secondary (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 5. Climate of Opinion and Tenant Turnover (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 6. Tenant Responses to Climate of Opinion: Autonomy, Defiance, and Morale (Box 388)
          - 7. Climate of Opinion and Interracial Adjustment (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 8. Changing Climate of Opinion (Empty) (Box 388)
        - Appendix: Account of Research Procedures
          - 1. First Steps: Setting the Problem
            - a. Practical Problems (Empty) (Box 388)
            - b. Orientation Toward Policy (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 2. Basic Principles of Research Procedure (Empty)
            - a. Quantitative and Qualitative Techniques (Box 388)
            - b. The Dynamic Approach (Empty) (Box 388)
            - c. Research Teams: Technical Necessity and Its Implications (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 3. Design of Inquiry (Empty)
            - a. Exploratory Field Trip (Empty) (Box 388)
            - b. Criteria for Selection Projects (Empty) (Box 388)
            - c. Pattern of Research (Empty)
              - 1. Qualitative Field Observation (Box 388)
              - 2. Initial Analysis (Box 388)
              - 3. Quantitative Field Observation (Box 388)
              - 4. Composite Analysis (Empty) (Box 388)
              - 5. Pattern of Overlapping Interview Schedules (Box 388)
            - d. Critique of Design (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 4. Problems of Field Work
            - a. Techniques for Obtaining Community Rapport
              - 1. Top Level Cooperation (Box 388)
              - 2. Multiple Entry into a Local Community (Box 388)
              - 3. Sources of Resistance to Research (Empty) (Box 388)
              - 4. Social Functions of Research for Tenants (Box 388)
            - c. Formal Interviewing
              - 1. Sampling (Box 388)
              - 2. Reliability (Empty) (Box 388)
            - d. Critique of Field Work (Empty) (Box 388)
            - e. Field Work Techniques: A Summary (Empty) (Box 388)
          - 5. Analysis and Interpretation (Empty)
            - a. Theory Oriented to Policy (Box 388)
            - b. Analysis of Data of Different Levels (Empty) (Box 388)
            - c. Cross-tabulations (Box 388)
        - Theory of Research Budget (Box 388)
        - Outsiders Attitude (Empty) (Box 388)
        - Co-Op: Symbol of Tenant Morale (Box 388)
        - Participation (Empty) (Box 388)
        - Segmentation (Empty) (Box 388)
        - Class (Empty) (Box 388)
        - Permanence (Box 388)
        - First Contact (Box 388)
        - School (Box 388)
        - Fire Department (Box 388)
        - Mutual Aid (Box 388)
        - Winfield--Physical Plant Today (Box 388)
        - Origin--Pre June 1941 (Box 388)
        - Site Selection-Neighborhood (Box 388)
        - Tenanting (Box 388)
        - Physical Condition (Empty) (Box 388)
        - Administration: Government (Box 388)
        - Separate Township (Box 388)
        - Administration: Tenants (Box 388)
        - Appraisal Today: Co-Op (Box 388)
        - First Newspaper (Box 388)
        - Police and Fire Department (Box 388)
        - Truman Investigation (Box 388)
        - Democratic Club (Box 388)
        - Nursery School (Box 388)
        - End of First Year Appraisal (Box 388)
        - School (Box 388)
        - Independents (Box 388)
        - Child Care Center (Box 388)
        - Community Center (Box 388)
        - Public Images and Tenant Morale (Box 388)
        - Intro-Orientation (Empty) (Box 388)
        - Density (Box 388)
        - Maintenance (Box 388)
        - Mobility (Box 388)
        - Journey to Work (Box 388)
        - Stigma of Public Housing (Box 388)
        - Epithets (Box 389)
        - Management Staff (Box 389)
        - Vacates (Box 389)
        - June (Box 389)
        - History--Clippings (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Conditions of Change (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Invasion (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Facilities (Box 389)
        - August (Box 389)
        - September (Box 389)
        - October (Box 389)
        - Patterns of Community Integration (Box 389)
        - Variation of Social Arrangements with Different Population Compositions (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Changes in Patterns of Family Living (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Relationship of Structural Aspects of Project to Patterns of Living (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Differences in Administration: Policy and Practice (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Different Relationships Between Project and Surrounding Areas- Different Patterns of Social Life (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Influence of Institutional Aspects of Planned Housing: Including Legal Requirements (Empty) (Box 389)
        - Social Organization: Formal and Informal (Box 389)
        - Interview Excerpts Organized by Interviewees Last Name--A-Z (Box 389)
        - Theory of Suggregate-Supergregate Relations (Box 390)
          - Class and Caste (Box 390)
          - In-and-Out Group (Box 390)
          - Rationalizations (Box 390)
          - Stereotypes and Attitudes (Box 390)
          - Definitions of Race (Box 390)
          - Functional Analysis (Box 390)
          - "Biological" Aspects of Race and Nationality (Box 390)
        - Cultural Backgrounds of Suggregates
          - Mexicans (Box 390)
          - Italians (Box 390)
          - Jews--General (Box 390)
          - Chinese (Box 390)
          - Negroes (Box 390)
          - Japanese (Box 390)
          - Poles (Box 390)
          - American Indians (Box 390)
          - Russians (Box 390)
        - Cultural Backgrounds of Supergregates
          - Chinese (Box 390)
          - Mexicans (Box 390)
          - Italians (Box 390)
          - Negroes (Box 390)
          - Jews (Box 390)
          - American Indians (Box 390)
          - Poles (Box 390)
          - Russians (Box 390)
        - Inter-Groupal Processes
          - Contact (Box 390)
          - Competition (Box 390)
          - Conflict (Box 390)
          - Accommodation (Box 390)
          - Assimilation (Box 390)
          - Amalgamation (Box 390)
          - Visibility (Box 390)
          - Suggregate Assimilates Supergregate Standards (Box 390)
          - Intermarriage
            - Theory of Intermarriage Factors Hindering Facilitating (Box 390)
            - Sex Differentials (Empty) (Box 390)
            - Generation Differentials (Empty) (Box 390)
            - Class Differentials (Empty) (Box 390)
            - Fertility of (Empty) (Box 390)
            - Assortative (Empty) (Box 390)
            - Felicity of (Empty) (Box 390)
        - Intra-Groupal Processes
          - Intra-Ethnic Discrimination (Box 390)
          - Crime (Box 390)
          - Products of S-S Relations (Box 390)
          - Suggregate Personality Types (Box 390)
          - Struggle for Status (Box 390)
          - Hybrids and Marginal Men (Box 390)
        - Fiction on Suggregates (Box 390)
        - City
          - Ecology (Box 390)
          - Theory: Growth of City Patterns (Box 390)
          - Specialization in City (Box 390)
          - Medieval City (Box 390)
          - Metropolis (Box 390)
          - General Considerations (Box 390)
          - Greek Cities (Box 390)
          - Roman Cities (Box 390)
    - Notes
      - General, 1995-2002, undated (Box 391, Folder 1)
      - D.E. Morrison on Paul Lazarsfeld, circa 2002 (Box 391, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files and Topical Interests
      - A Fortiori Reasoning, undated (Box 391, Folder 3)
      - Accumulation of Advantage
        - General, 1975-1986, (2 Folders) (Box 391, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Bibliography, 1978-1980 (Box 391, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 391, Folder 7)
        - Matthew Effect, 1949, 1973-1986 (Box 391, Folder 8)
      - "Acquaintance With" and "Knowledge About," 1966-1988 (Box 391, Folder 9)
      - Affirming the Consequent as Fallacy of Science, 1984-1985, undated (Box 391, Folder 10)
      - Age, Old, Intellectual Self-Management, 1982 (Box 391, Folder 11)
      - Altruism and Norms in Science, 1987-1992 (Box 391, Folder 12)
      - Anticipatory Socialization, 1951-1977 (Box 391, Folder 13)
      - Anticipatory Socialization, 1951-1977 (Box 392, Folder 1)
      - Attitudes and Behaviors, 1975-1977 (Box 392, Folder 2)
      - Authorial Tics, 1987 (Box 392, Folder 3)
      - Baconian Sociology, 1964, 1985-1987 (Box 392, Folder 4)
      - "Blaming the Victim" and "The Joys of Victimhood," 1989 (Box 392, Folder 5)
      - Carrollean File (Lewis Carroll), 1986, undated (Box 392, Folder 6)
      - Climate of Opinion, 1989-1990 (Box 392, Folder 7)
      - Cognitive Conduits, 1980-1988 (Box 392, Folder 8)
      - Cognitive Relativism, 1991 (Box 392, Folder 9)
      - Coincidences, 1976-1986 (Box 392, Folder 10)
      - Concept of "The Influential," 1988-1994 (Box 392, Folder 11)
      - Controversy and Polemic Misunderstandings in Science, 1950-1952, 1972-1989, (3 Folders) (Box 392, Folder 12 to 14)
      - "Copernican Revolution" in Sociology of Knowledge, 1983-1985 (Box 393, Folder 1)
      - Creative Typos and Lovely Slips, 1975-1989 (Box 393, Folder 2)
      - Cryptomnesia, 1970-1988 (Box 393, Folder 3)
      - Dangers of Erudition, undated (Box 393, Folder 4)
      - Deadlines: A Dead Metaphor that Persists in Becoming Alive, 1994 (Box 393, Folder 5)
      - Disciplined Eclecticism, 1960-1986, (3 Folders) (Box 393, Folder 6 to 8)
      - Displacement of Goals, 1968-1977 (Box 393, Folder 9)
      - Dogsbody, 1983 (Box 393, Folder 10)
      - Elegiac Lament Regarding Young, Dead Scientists, undated (Box 393, Folder 11)
      - Epithets, Theory of, 1961-1971, undated (Box 393, Folder 12)
      - Establishing the Phenomenon, 1987-1997 (Box 393, Folder 13)
      - Ethos of Science (Box 394)
        - General, 1966-1989 (Box 394, Folder 1)
        - and Democracy, 1983-1998 (Box 394, Folder 2)
      - Ex Ante and Ex Post, 1968-2000 (Box 394, Folder 3)
      - Ex Ungue Leonem, 1977-1995 (Box 394, Folder 4)
      - Extrinsic Rewards and Intrinsic Motivation, 1999-2000 (Box 394, Folder 5)
      - Fact as Theory Laden/Sociological Fact, 1949-1988 (Box 394, Folder 6)
      - Fads in Science, 1977-1989 (Box 394, Folder 7)
      - Falsification, Naive: Conceptual Infanticide; Premature Rejection, 1974-1988, (2 Folders) (Box 394, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Fathers and Mothers of Science, 1980-1986 (Box 394, Folder 10)
      - Festschrift
        - Citation Analysis, 1991-1992 (Box 395, Folder 1)
        - Concept and History of, 1989-1996 (Box 395, Folder 2)
        - Notes and Research, 1970, 1991-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 395, Folder 3 to 4)
        - Reward System, 1989-1992 (Box 395, Folder 5)
        - Various Languages and Dictionaries, undated (Box 395, Folder 6)
      - Four-fold Table, 2001 (Box 395, Folder 7)
      - Fraud in Science, 1984-1988 (Box 395, Folder 8)
      - Functions as Distinct from Motives, 2000 (Box 395, Folder 9)
      - Gender Syntax Problem (His/Her, He/She), 1988-1995 (Box 395, Folder 10)
      - Graffiti, 1976-1984 (Box 395, Folder 11)
      - Group Loyalties and Salient Statuses, 1992 (Box 395, Folder 12)
      - Haunting Presence of the Functionally Irrelevant Attributes
        - General, 1988-2002, (3 Folders) (Box 396, Folder 1 to 3)
        - Status Activation, 1964, 1994, undated (Box 396, Folder 4)
      - Houdini, Harry, 1990-1999 (Box 396, Folder 5)
      - Hyperexis, 1987 (Box 396, Folder 6)
      - Imagination--Use of Term, undated (Box 396, Folder 7)
      - Incentives, undated (Box 396, Folder 8)
      - Institutionalized Evasions
        - General, 1979-1984 (Box 396, Folder 9)
        - of Institutional Norms, 1993-1997 (Box 396, Folder 10)
      - Intellectual Property
        - General, 1990 (Box 396, Folder 11)
        - in Science, 1980 (Box 396, Folder 12)
      - Intensified Ascribed Identities, 1993 (Box 396, Folder 13)
      - "Ism" as Suffix Indicating Excess, undated (Box 396, Folder 14)
      - "Labelling [sic] Theory" and Watergate, 1973 (Box 396, Folder 15)
      - Limited Sloppiness and Kindred Ideas, 1981-1992 (Box 396, Folder 16)
      - Locals and Cosmopolitans
        - General, 1973-1991 (Box 396, Folder 17)
        - General, 1973-1991 (Box 397, Folder 1)
        - Rosabeth M. Kanter Style, 1995 (Box 397, Folder 2)
      - Matthew Effect
        - General, 1988-2000 (Box 397, Folder 3)
        - Distributive Justice, 1947-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 397, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Mea Culpa--"I am Guilty Because…," 1986 (Box 397, Folder 6)
      - Middle-Range Theory, 1948-1984, (3 Folders) (Box 397, Folder 7 to 9)
      - Moral Implications of Sociological Analysis, 1987 (Box 398, Folder 1)
      - Multiples, 1978-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 398, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Musings and Phrasings, 1983-1999 (Box 398, Folder 4)
      - Neo-Functionalism, 1983-1995 (Box 398, Folder 5)
      - Neo-Utilitarianism
        - in Science, 1970, (2 Folders) (Box 398, Folder 6 to 7)
        - In Sociology, 1970-1973 (Box 398, Folder 8)